Miss.
Someone asked me to give you this box.
Thank you.
Western outskirts, noon.
Trade the Coastal Defense Map for Li Mingyuan.
Don't let anyone know.
Otherwise, his head rolls.
We won't wait.
Young Master,
what happened to you?
It's nothing.
Ran into some reckless robbers.
Fired a few shots,
and drove them off.
Miss Jiang didn't say a word
and suddenly took off.
We found this in her room.
Behave yourself!
Li Mingyuan,
you're quite clever,
teaming up with Lian Ye to fool me so completely.
Too bad
you have such an idiot by your side.
Such a clumsy trick,
yet it actually lured her out.
What will it take for you to let her go?
Hand over your last Coastal Defense Map.
No! Without the Coastal Defense Map,
I'm not worth saving!
You can't give him the Coastal Defense Map!
I'm not worth it!
You don't get a say here!
Are you trading or not?
I'll trade.
Go.
At least you still have a conscience.
She didn't risk her life for you in vain.
Go.
It's my fault.
I made everyone's efforts go to waste.
I deserve to die.
I was so stupid.
It's okay. Trust me.
I thought I'd never see you again.
Sister Dieyi, I'm sorry.
It's all my fault for being so reckless.
The Coastal Defense Map is now in Sun Hanji's hands.
Don't blame yourself.
Anyone would have chosen to save a life.
Mr. Matsui, Mr. Matsui!
I've recovered the complete Coastal Defense Map
to do my humble part for the Major General's cause!
You idiot!
Look for yourself!
This...
Who did this?
Are you asking me?
I... I...
I really don't know!
Brother Mingyuan, it's all up to you now.
If we didn't need every man right now,
I'd have your heads chopped off!
You're all stripped of your ranks
and demoted to private second class.
In future battles, kill more Japanese
to redeem yourselves!
Yes, sir!
Pass down the order.
Adjust troop deployments.
Redraw the Coastal Defense Map.
Yes, sir.
Come on out.
Mingyuan, using the Japanese as cover,
you printed the Coastal Defense Map in the papers.
Blurring truth and falsehood,
so everyone could see it.
After all, they can't punish everyone, right?
You forced our hand to alter the Coastal Defense Map,
turning real into fake,
just to clear those in the know.
What sheer audacity!
Senior, circumstances forced my hand.
I had no other choice.
Reckless insubordination!
Death is too good for you!
Drifting like weeds in troubled times,
what did the common folk do wrong?
A soft heart cannot lead an army.
I'm not a commander.
I'm just an ordinary police officer.
Fine, fine.
This time, your merits balance out your faults.
Clean up all the loose ends for me.
Don't let me hear any rumors,
or I'll hold you solely responsible.
I'll get it done, sir.
Ji Chunyue, you damn bitch!
Did you help those sluts
collude with Chen Dieyi?
So what if I did?
You've completely lost your mind!
Tell me where those bitches are!
I'll slaughter every last one of them!
You trapped me here in Minchun Pavilion,
making me commit all kinds of atrocities.
I'm no better than an executioner!
I deserve to die!
You...
Put out the fire, quick!
It's over. Everything is ruined.
Li Mingyuan.
Lian Ye.
What on earth do you want?
We brought all these people
to settle scores with you.
Sun Hanji,
you're suspected in multiple homicides.
Come to the station with us for questioning.
Listen up, Shipboard Guild!
Anyone not involved in the murders
is welcome to join our Sanshan Gang.
The past will be forgiven,
and we start fresh.
I dare any of you to move!
Any accomplices involved,
turn yourselves in right now,
and the police will show leniency!
All of you, attack!
Out of the way!
What do you want?
Did you have someone burn down my family home?
So what if I did?
Was it you
who sent Chen Dieyi to Minchun Pavilion?
It was me.
This arm
is payback for Chen Dieyi.
This is payback for Bai Yumei.
This is payback for Liu Furong.
This is payback for the countless souls
who died brutally at your hands!
Who's the one controlling you behind the scenes?
A man...
the higher he climbs,
the-the more he reeks of blood.
If I tell you, will you spare me?
I'll consider it.
It's that Japanese dog, Jiichiro Matsui!
He hates the Lian family.
He swore to make the Lians
slaves and whores for generations!
He forced me to do it!
Slaves and whores...
Yes, slaves and whores!
It has nothing to do with me!
Spare me! I can be your dog!
You said... you wouldn't kill me!